Proverbs chapter 22 verse 29.
The Bible says, "Do you see a man who
excels
in his work?
He will stand before kings.
He will not stand before
unknown men." Let me read that verse
again.
"Do you see a man who excels
in his work?
He will stand before kings.
He will not stand before
unknown men." Father, in the name of
Jesus Christ, thank you for this
privilege of uh
afforded us this morning to come to your
house to worship you,
to hear your word.
I pray, Lord, that you anoint me, Lord,
to do justice to the text before us and
this great day in our
Christian calendar.
May heaven rejoice, oh God. Enable me,
Lord Jesus Christ,
to be your mouthpiece.
In Jesus' name I pray.
Amen. Be seated, please.
I want to speak on the subject I've
entitled becoming
valuable.
Becoming
The Bible says that we were lost
people.
The Bible says we were people without
hope
and a future.
The scripture says that we were lost in
sin and in darkness, separated from the
love of God.
A people who are far from God and were
not in the Commonwealth of Israel.
That it had to take the coming of Jesus
Christ
to come and to die an ignominious death
at the cross
as a common criminal
to be persecuted, uh hung high on the
cross, and stretched wide.
Finally had to die and resurrect so that
a people that were lost, separated from
God,
far from the grace and the love of God
could be brought close to God and have
communion and then then they can cry
Abba Father.
And that can they can be called a people
one more time.
Brothers and sisters, ladies and
gentlemen,
I come on this Resurrection Sunday
to remind you that the death and the
resurrection of Jesus Christ did one
thing which is so crucial and it was to
make you valuable.
Because without the resurrection of
Jesus Christ, we are
despicable people.
Debauched.
Without hope and without a future.
Having a Christless eternity.
And if there's anything that the death
and the resurrection of Jesus Christ
does,
is to resurrect the hopes which were
lost.
Resurrect a future
that we would never have envisioned or
even imagined.
I want to tell you, church, that it
pains God to see that after his death
and resurrection, that people in the
church and people
who know him still live their lives as
if they are nothing and as if they are
not valuable.
In fact, it is
a crucifixion of Jesus Christ a second
time.
To the world, when people think that you
run to church because you have problems.
And that the people in the church are
people
who have not made it out there.
There is a deep truth
that many people ignore.
My brothers and sisters, I want to
declare to you this morning that success
is not attracted by a need.
Success is attracted by value.
If you came to listen to that point
alone, it was worth your coming. I want
to repeat, success is not attracted by
need.
Success is attracted
by value.
For you see in life many people want
access.
Few people offer substance.
Why do you want access to me?
Why do you want to be close to me?
What are you bringing in my life?
WHAT ARE YOU CARRYING
TO COME to me?
Yes.
God died and rose again to make us
valuable people.
For you see, ladies and gentlemen,
brothers and sisters,
successful people are constantly
surrounded by voices asking, pulling,
demanding. There is no pressure that you
would ever know, but until you get
successful, you will know what it is to
be successful because you will be
surrounded by all sorts of voices, need,
calls, text messages. People will
surround you with all sorts of things
around. And I'm telling you today that
when you are successful, then you get to
understand that you will not be drawn to
those who are calling and pulling, but
you'll be drawn by people who bring
solution, strength, and substance.
Successful people HAVE GOT TOO MANY
CROWDS.
BUT THOSE DON'T APPEAL TO THEM.
SUCCESSFUL people are drawn to those who
bring solution,
strength,
and substance.
I came TO CHALLENGE YOU THIS UH
Sunday to stop just being another
person,
but to become a valuable person.
I want you to help me preach and tell
your neighbor, "Please uh just become a
valuable person."
Oh, yeah. Tell him, "Become a valuable
Just not another person, but become
a valuable person."
What do you mean, Bishop? Yes, the death
and the resurrection of Jesus came to
make us valuable. Then, how are you
going to become valuable? A few points
that I'm going to leave with you and
I'll be out of your face. Number one, if
you're going to be valuable, just like
Jesus expects you to be, the first thing
you have to do is to master a valuable
skill.
Ecclesiastes chapter 10 and verse 10
says, "If the iron be blunt,
then you will use a lot of energy,
but wisdom is profitable to direct."
Value begins with what you can do.
Ecclesiastes chapter 10 and verse 10,
"If the ax is dull, and one does not
sharpen the edge, then he must use more
strength, but wisdom
brings success."
Brothers and sisters, ladies and
gentlemen, let me ask you, what is it
that you are known for?
WHAT IS IT THAT WHEN PEOPLE see you can
say that you are known for? What skill
do you bring into this world? What
solutions do YOU CARRY? WHAT SUPPORT do
you give? Yes, to become valuable, you
must master a valuable skill. And this
is the foundation. If you're going to be
valuable to anybody and to this world
and to this country, you must have
something that you carry. Touch somebody
this morning and tell them you must have
something that you carry. You cannot
just be A PERSON WHO CARRIES NOTHING.
YOU CANNOT JUST BE A PERSON WHO HAS NO
SOLUTION. AND LET ME TELL YOU THIS
MORNING, I feel like I'm going to preach
this morning THAT IF YOU HAVE NO
SOLUTION, YOU ARE THE PROBLEM.
What solution do YOU BRING?
IN EVERY ORGANIZATION and even IN THE
CHURCH, THE PEOPLE WHO don't bring any
solution, THEY ARE THE PROBLEM.
OH, YEAH. I DON'T WANT YOU TO LOOK AT
YOUR NEIGHBOR THIS morning and tell them
are you the solution or the problem? But
just look at them and smile and tell
them
don't don't don't don't please tell
them. BUT IF YOU ARE NOT THE SOLUTION,
YOU ARE THE PROBLEM. WHAT IS IT THAT you
are known for?
What skills do you bring? Is it writing?
Is it design? Is it technology? Is it
leadership? What solution do you bring?
PROBLEM-SOLVING ABILITY. WHAT SUPPORT DO
YOU GIVE TO THIS WORLD? THERE MUST BE
SOMETHING IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE VALUABLE
THAT YOU ARE KNOWN FOR. WHAT IS IT THAT
WHEN I LOOK AT YOU THAT YOU ARE KNOWN
FOR BECAUSE THE DEATH AND THE
RESURRECTION OF JESUS CHRIST CAME TO
MAKE YOU
VALUABLE.
IT came to make you valuable.
AND WHEN I LOOK AROUND THE WORLD, I feel
sorry. And sometimes I wonder
if you really acknowledge what it means
for Jesus to die and to resurrect with
hope and power
over death held in the grave.
You want to be valuable.
Yes.
You have to master one useful skill.
Sharpen it until it becomes rare.
Become excellent and not average.
Help me preach, please. Please stand up
on your feet. Look for two people and
tell them become excellent and not
average. Please tell them that. BECOME
EXCELLENT AND NOT AVERAGE. PLEASE TELL
THEM. OH, COME ON. PLEASE TELL THEM
BECOME EXCELLENT AND NOT AVERAGE. BECOME
EXCELLENT AND NOT AVERAGE.
HALLELUJAH.
SIT DOWN. LET ME TALK TO YOU this
Resurrection Sunday.
AVERAGE DOES NOT sell anymore.
IT IS TOO CROWDED
IN THE ARENA OF AVERAGE.
THERE'S TOO MUCH TRAFFIC ON THE ARENA OF
AVERAGE. THE DEATH AND THE RESURRECTION
OF JESUS CHRIST CAME TO MAKE YOU
VALUABLE. AND FOR YOU TO BE VALUABLE,
ladies and gentlemen, BROTHERS AND
SISTERS, YOU HAVE TO BE A PERSON WHO
OPERATES IN THE SPIRIT OF EXCELLENCE.
THAT MEANS WHATEVER YOU TOUCH TURNS TO
GOLD. WHATEVER YOU DO, NOBODY CAN DO IT
LIKE YOU DO IT. WHEN YOU GET TO DO IT
LIKE YOU DO IT LIKE YOU DO IT. OH, COME
ON. SOMEBODY. YOU'VE GOT TO BE SOMEBODY
WHO IS KNOWN FOR WHAT YOU DO.
WHAT ARE YOU KNOWN FOR?
WHY DID JESUS DIE FOR YOU?
WHO ARE YOU? WHAT ARE YOU DOING? THE
DEATH OF JESUS CHRIST CAME TO MAKE YOU
IMPACTFUL.
IT CAME TO MAKE YOU A PERSON WHO WALKS
AND OPERATES IN THE SPIRIT OF
EXCELLENCE. IF YOU'RE WRITING, NOBODY
CAN write for you LIKE YOU. IF YOU'RE
COOKING, NOBODY CAN COOK LIKE YOU. IF
YOU'RE DRIVING, NO ONE CAN DRIVE LIKE
YOU. OH, COME ON. AM I TALKING TO
SOMEBODY HERE? THIS IS WHAT IT MEANS BY
THE DEATH AND THE RESURRECTION OF JESUS
CHRIST. IT CAME TO MAKE YOU VALUABLE.
WHATEVER YOU DO, YOU DO IT IN THE SPIRIT
OF
HALLELUJAH.
YES.
You have to be valuable because God
has sent His Son.
If you're going to be valuable, you have
to upgrade your mind.
Romans chapter 12:2 says, "Be
transformed by the renewing of your
mind."
Yeah.
You don't attract what you want.
Listen to this. You attract what you
are.
You don't attract what you want.
You attract what you are.
And I just want to give you a test this
morning even as I preach this morning in
my introductory remarks
and ask you,
"What are you attracting?"
What are you attracting?
You want to know what you're attracting?
That's exactly what you are.
Don't look for a prophet to come from
Ghana or from Nigeria or from wherever
they come from
to come and give you a telephone number
as if you're so stupid you can't know
your telephone number yourself. Oh, come
on. You need to look around yourself and
see WHO ARE YOU ATTRACTING? THAT IS
EXACTLY WHO YOU ARE.
I don't have to come here, close my
eyes, and then you know, frame my words
to you and give you a prophetic word of
who you are. I just need to look around
the people you are attracting. The
people you are attracting are exactly
who you are.
So, the Bible says that
if you're going to be valuable, you've
got to grade your mind.
Successful people avoid complainers,
excuse makers,
negative thinkers.
Successful people,
valuable people,
are attracted to solution carriers,
vision thinkers,
and growth-minded people.
Your mindset
is
your magnet.
Yes, stop thinking survival,
start thinking impact.
Replace complainers
and people
who bring solution.
Train your mind
daily. The scripture tells us renew your
mind. Let your mind be transformed.
There is no bigger miracle, to me, to
me,
to me, than transformed mind.
There is no bigger miracle than a
transformed mind.
Being transformed in your mind is bigger
than a walking.
than a blind eye being opened.
For you can have your eyes open and you
can still have you walking yourself, but
I'm telling you if your mind is not
transformed, you will not move from
point A to B. That is the greatest
deliverance that anyone can get by
transforming their mind.
Transforming
their mind.
Yes, the death
and the resurrection of Jesus Christ
came to make us valuable people.
But you're going to be valuable,
thirdly,
you must master communication.
For you see,
communication is
your access tool.
I repeat, communication is your access
tool. Proverbs 18:21 says, "Death and
life are in the power
of the tongue."
You may be extremely educated.
Listen to me. You may be a professor
with too much knowledge,
but if you cannot communicate,
you will not be valuable.
You must be a communicator
if you're going to be a valuable person.
You may be skilled,
but if you cannot communicate, you will
be ignored.
I'm telling you the truth.
What opens doors is communication, is
clarity, is confidence, is respect.
YOU CANNOT BE A VALUABLE person who has
not mastered the art of communication.
You have to be able to talk. You have to
be able to express yourself. You have to
be able to put out the knowledge that
you have. You have to be because by the
way, let me tell you how then do you
interact with people? YOU INTERACT WITH
PEOPLE BY COMMUNICATION. YOU HAVE TO
HAVE CLARITY in your talking because I
have met some professors, and I've met
SOME GREAT DOCTORS, AND I'VE ALSO MET
SOME GOVERNMENT SPOKESPEOPLE WHO CANNOT
EVEN EXPRESS WHAT THEY'RE TRYING TO TELL
ME. BUT IF YOU GET SOMEBODY WHO KNOWS
HOW TO COMMUNICATE, LET ME TELL YOU,
THEY BECOME VALUABLE. THEY STAND OUT.
THERE'S CLARITY. BUT YOU CANNOT BE A
PROFESSOR. YOU CANNOT BE A VALUABLE
PERSON THAT CANNOT EVEN COMMUNICATE.
YOU HAVE TO IMPROVE THE GIFT OF THE GAP.
YOU HAVE TO LEARN HOW TO TALK.
HOW DO YOU LIVE WITH PEOPLE AND YOU
CANNOT TALK? AND BY THE WAY, HOW DO YOU
BECOME A LEADER AND YOU CANNOT EVEN
EXPRESS THE VISION OF WHERE YOU WANT THE
PEOPLE to go.
YOU WANT TO BE A VALUABLE PERSON?
YOU HAVE TO TELL THE VISION. YOU HAVE TO
TELL THE MISSION. YOU HAVE TO SPEAK OUT
THE GOALS SO THAT PEOPLE CAN KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT YOU'RE COMMUNICATING. YOU
PASS ON KNOWLEDGE BY COMMUNICATION. AND
I KNOW VERY WELL IT'S NOT THAT YOU'RE
STUPID. IT'S NOT THAT YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING, but you don't know
how to communicate.
FOR YOU TO BE VALUABLE, LISTEN TO ME.
YOU HAVE TO be
a communicator.
EVEN IN BUSINESS, YOU HAVE to be a
communicator.
YOU HAVE TO TALK TO ME.
YOU HAVE TO EX-
EXPLAIN TO ME
IN A MANNER THAT I CAN UNDERSTAND FOR ME
TO BUY YOUR STUFF.
YOU CANNOT
BE A VALUABLE PERSON IN THIS WORLD.
AND YOU CANNOT COMMUNICATE
WHAT YOU KNOW
OR what you're giving
or what you're trying to express.
So the scripture says,
life
and death
are in the POWER
OF THE TONGUE.
CAN I give you some more?
For you to be a valuable person,
you have to be consistent and reliable.
Luke chapter 16 and verse 10 says, "He
that is faithful in that which is least
faithful
in that which
is least." Successful people don't
gamble with unreliable people.
Successful people don't gamble with
unreliable
people.
I started pastoring from a very early
age.
Very early age. Early 20s.
Early 20s.
I think at the age of 23 I had actually
graduated from Bible College.
Graduated.
Yeah.
At the age of 23.
Of course I pushed on.
Did other degrees after that. But at the
age of 23, I started pastoring.
And I learned long time ago
that working with consistent people
is far
better
than working with talented people who
are not consistent.
I have no time AT ALL
FOR PEOPLE WHO ARE GIFTED and talented
who are not consistent.
I have no business with you. You go and
play your saxophone in another church.
Don't play it here.
That you are here one Sunday and the
next Sunday I want you you're not there.
You're not consistent.
You are in a praise and worship or one
practice and the next one you're not.
Just go and sing in your choir at home.
CONSISTENCY.
BEING FAITHFUL IN THE LEAST.
OH GOD ALMIGHTY.
I would like to admonish you to read a
book that was written way back there.
The title of the book is Finishing
Strong.
And the title talks about three
preachers.
One of them was Billy Graham.
And among the three preachers, Billy
Graham was the poorest preacher.
The rest could preach the roof down.
They would preach fire and brimstone.
They were the known preachers.
But they did not continue preaching.
Billy Graham was the least of all those
preachers at that particular time.
Nobody knew BILLY GRAHAM, BUT BILLY
GRAHAM CONTINUED being consistent.
He was always THERE WHEN HE NEEDED. HE
was always in crusades. The others who
were so gifted with the gift of the gap,
they could speak a golden tongue. Let me
tell you, THEY FADED OFF. BUT THE
CONSISTENT BILLY GRAHAM emerged
eventually as the greatest evangelist
who has ever lived, brought hundreds and
millions OF PEOPLE, MET ALMOST ALL THE
PRESIDENTS FROM THE 1960S UNTIL HIS
DEATH. WHY? CONSISTENCY.
BEING CONSISTENT.
BEING THERE
IS THE KEY TO BECOME VALUABLE. YOU ARE
CAN BE COUNTED UPON. WE CAN PREDICT WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DO. WE CAN PREDICT WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DELIVER. WE CAN PREDICT
WHAT YOU CARRY BECAUSE YOU ARE
CONSISTENT. CAN I GIVE YOU another
story?
I had a meeting with the Carnivore
directors, the three top CARNIVORE
DIRECTORS.
BACK THEN
because I used to go to Carnivore.
I have some meat.
That's some very good meat.
You can eat whatever you want.
Even some meat that is not available in
the butchery, you can afford it, you can
get it there.
Uh if you're adventurous, you can even
eat the crocodile.
All right?
You can eat the crocodile.
You
Some of you have not eaten the
crocodile. When you eat the crocodile,
your theology of the crocodile will
change.
You'll be seeing the crocodile basking
and you'll be salivating.
So, I sat down with them.
They're my good friends.
And I said, "How come Carnivore is still
doing very well years later
from the '70s, early '70s, you're still
doing very, very well?
How come people are still flocking at
Carnivore? Restaurants have come and
gone. It looks like, you know,
restaurants have got a a lifespan, you
know? It's just like these clubs, they
open, they have a lifespan. They come
and they hit for 4, 3 years or maximum 5
years and they die. You go after 4, 5
years, you don't wonder if it's the same
place you went to because THEY HAVE A
LIFESPAN." THEY SAID, "NO, NO, NO, NO,
for us we're different." I said, "What's
the difference?"
I'll never forget the answer they gave
me. They told me, "Listen,
at Carnivore,
the meat we started with, the quality of
meat, how it is done with excellence, is
the same way we do it today. We have
never changed the quality of how we do
our meat. And that's why people can come
because when you go to Carnival, their
meat is predictable.
Go to some of these other places. TODAY
YOU HAVE VERY good meat.
Excellent meat. And you think that if
you go there next month, it is your
mother's birthday, you'll have the same
meat. You go there and you'll get SO
DISAPPOINTED. THE SAME place same
place same name. The meat you ate last
month, you come after a month, you
wonder my goodness and you leave there
complaining because they are they are
NOT CONSISTENT. TO BECOME A VALUABLE
PERSON, YOU'VE GOT TO BE CONSISTENT.
I'VE GOT TO PREDICT what you will do,
WHAT YOU WILL DELIVER.
NOT HAPHAZARD. ONE TIME YOU'RE HIGH, ONE
TIME YOU'RE LOW, ONE TIME YOU CAN DO
WELL, THE OTHER TIME YOU CAN'T DO WELL.
AND THAT OH PLEASE, I DON'T WANT PEOPLE
WHO ARE NOT CONSISTENT. OH YES, EVEN AS
A BISHOP WHEN I'M GIVING YOU THE
MICROPHONE, I want you to be consistent.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SITTING HERE AND I'M
CROSSING MY FINGERS. WHAT ARE THEY GOING
TO SAY NEXT? WHAT ARE THEY GOING TO SAY
NEXT? ARE THEY GOING TO BLOW UP? ARE
THEY GOING TO MESS UP THEIR THEOLOGY AND
THEIR DOCTRINES HERE? I WANT TO BE THERE
COMFORTABLE KNOWING THAT IT'S GOING TO
FLOW. LOOK AT SOMEBODY AND SAY YOU'VE
GOT TO BE CONSISTENT.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE CONSISTENT.
Consistency
makes you
valuable.
Are you hearing me?
Consistency
I even don't know how people live their
relationships by the way.
CUZ IT GOES DOWN TO RELATIONSHIPS.
I DON'T know what to make of you.
I don't know what TO MAKE OF YOU.
One time you're very nice and happy, the
next moment you're like, you know,
everything has changed.
And I'm not saying that your Jesus
Christ was the same yesterday, today,
and forevermore.
But I do know that consistency even in
relationship helps in augmenting the
relationship.
And being unpredictable is a one OF THE
MOST DIFFICULT THINGS TO DEAL WITH.
Because I don't know what to expect.
I mean, I can be sitting in the sitting
room and I hear a slap, pop.
Jesus.
What is this?
Look at your neighbor and say, "You have
got to be consistent if you're going to
be valuable."
No wonder the Bible says Jesus Christ is
does not change, he's consistent.
Or pre- Praise the Lord. He is
consistent. YOU CAN COUNT ON HIS LOVE.
You can count on his faithfulness. He is
not going to be there to DISAPPOINT YOU.
OH, COME ON, SOMETHING. HE SAID, "I WILL
BE WITH YOU ALL THE WAY. I WILL NOT
LEAVE YOU. I WILL NOT DISAPPOINT YOU."
HE'S CONSISTENT. IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE
VALUABLE, OH, HOUSE OF GRACE, IF YOU'RE
GOING TO BE VALUABLE ON THIS
RESURRECTION SUNDAY, YOU'VE GOT TO BE
CONSISTENT.
IT'S A QUALITY OF GOD.
Being consistent.
It's a quality
of God.
Yes.
This Resurrection Sunday,
Christ comes to remind us
that
his word up valuable people.
Valuable people.
Do what you say.
Finish what you start.
Be predictable in excellence.
Amen.
The other thing I want to mention here,
if you're going to be valuable,
you have to position yourself
strategically.
I want to mention here this morning
that environment
matters.
1 Corinthians chapter 15 and verse 33
says evil communication corrupts good
manners or morals.
I repeat, 1 Corinthians 15
and 33, evil communication
corrupts good
manners or
morals. You cannot attract
what you are never exposed to. You
cannot attract what you are never
exposed to. Everything that you have
attracted has been exposed
to you somehow. Environment controls
opportunities.
Yes, growth
happens in good environments.
Professional circles
make you professional. Purpose-driven
communities give purpose. Brothers and
sisters, ladies and gentlemen, if you're
going to be a valuable person, choose
your environment right.
You can plant two plants,
same breed. You can plant maize here,
all right? On fertile ground, it will
grow. Same seed. And you can take seed
again and plant it on another poor
environment, the one planted on poor
environment will not do well. It is NOT
THE PROBLEM OF THE SEED, it's the
problem of the environment.
It is a problem of the environment.
And some of you are not making it in
life because you are in the wrong
environment.
Your friendships are the wrong people.
Look around and see what environment you
are in because if you're going to be
valuable, listen to me, your environment
matters. You can be the seed in a jungle
and do poorly. You can take that same
seed and plant it ON FERTILE LOAMY SOIL
AND it will do very differently.
ENVIRONMENT
matters if you're going to be valuable.
YOU CANNOT BE RICH IF YOU DON'T surround
yourself with rich people.
WHAT IS YOUR ENVIRONMENT?
LOOK AT THE ENVIRONMENT YOU'RE PLANTING
YOURSELF IN.
And check
your success rate
in keeping with environment
you'll find yourself in.
Success
is often a matter of location.
Access is often
a matter of location.
So,
if you're in the wrong environment,
change if necessary.
Find a place where growth is happening.
Stop sitting where nothing
is growing, expecting that you are going
to be different.
Brothers and sisters, ladies and
gentlemen,
yes, Christ came to die and to
rise up again from the dead,
so that he can make us
valuable.
I had 10 points. I've given you five.
And my time is gone.
Allow me to continue with this message
next Sunday.
Please wake up on your feet.
Look for three people
and just tell them God
sent Jesus to die. Let me make it short.
Christ died
that you can become valuable.
Look for three people and tell them that
Christ died
that you can become valuable. Christ
died
that you can become valuable.
Hallelujah.
And after that, I want to make some
prophetic declaration over your life.
I want you to shout with your mouth
like you really mean it from your heart.
Say, "I declare
I'm rising
in value.
I declare
I will not be overlooked again.
I will not be overlooked again. I will
not be overlooked again. Doors will
open. Doors will open. Because Because
of what I carry. of what I carry. DOORS
WILL SHOUT ON THIS ONE. DOORS WILL OPEN
DOORS will open. BECAUSE OF WHAT I
CARRY.
>> BECAUSE OF WHAT I CARRY. SAY I WILL
STAND BEFORE KINGS
>> I WILL stand before kings AND I WILL NOT
BE AN ORDINARY PERSON.
>> AND I WILL NOT BE an ordinary person. My
life My life will COMMAND WILL COMMAND
ATTENTION ATTENTION
>> BY divine excellence.
>> BY DIVINE EXCELLENCE. MY LIFE MY LIFE
WILL COMMAND
>> WILL COMMAND ATTENTION ATTENTION BY
DIVINE EXCELLENCE.
>> BY DIVINE EXCELLENCE.
>> IN JESUS' NAME.
>> IN JESUS' NAME. IN JESUS' NAME. IN
JESUS' NAME. SOMEBODY PUT YOUR HANDS
TOGETHER FOR JESUS.
BEFORE YOUR presence came Hallelujah.
and changed
Oh, GIVE YOUR NEIGHBOR A HIGH FIVE AND
TELL HIM YOU'RE A PERSON OF VALUE.
>> GO BACK TO THE WAY I USED TO BE. I WON'T
go back to the way I used to be.
>> I won't Come on. Come on. Come on.
YOU'RE A PERSON OF VALUE.
I WON'T GO BACK.
>> I had 10 points. I've given you five.
The remaining ones are the ones which
are dangerous.
The remaining ones are very dangerous.
You cannot miss next Sunday. Look at
your neighbor. You cannot miss next
Sunday.
The remaining ones. Oh.
The remaining ones are dangerous.
After I finish this series
of value, which I'll finish next Sunday.
This was because of the resurrection
Sunday. To show you the death
and the resurrection of Jesus makes you
somebody.
It makes you somebody. It does NOT MAKE
YOU NOTHING.
It makes you somebody.
I know when I read that scripture,
people thought "Ooh, this is
Resurrection Sunday. What is he going to
preach about?"
You are a valuable person.
Amen. Please,
may Easter remind you how valuable you
are.
That he died for you.
How can you can't die for people are not
valuable? You are so valuable that he
died for you.
And they have gone to say that if you
are the only one in the world, he still
would have died for you. Put your hands
together for Jesus.
I want some of you to raise your
standards of living.
Live your life like a valuable person.
Please.
This is my advice, free of charge.
Are you listening to me? Don't carry
yourself like a nobody.
It is not permitted in House of Grace.
Look at somebody and say "It's not
permitted in House of Grace."
It's not permitted here.
Live your life like somebody.
The Bible says you've been bought
not with corruptible things of this
world.
And the things they mention there are
the things people run for.
Silver and gold, you see this, but you
have been bought
by the precious blood
of Jesus Christ.
One more time, look at somebody and tell
them you are valuable.
Hallelujah.
As you walk, walk like a valuable
person.
As you sit down to eat, eat like a
valuable person.
AS YOU DRIVE YOUR CAR, drive like a
Ah, come on, ON. HOUSE OF GRACE, ARE YOU
LISTENING TO ME? YOU'RE A VALUABLE
PERSON.
and favor
And because you're a valuable person,
in fact, I'm going to preach this. Maybe
I'll start with I'll preach this.
The reason why people misunderstand you
is because you're too valuable for them.
The reason why some people misunderstand
you, oh, you are too valuable for them.
Mediocrity and all that thing that is
down there, the traffic, traffic, you
left it, so they cannot understand you.
But you're valuable. One more time, tell
somebody you're very valuable.
You may be seated.
I won't go back. I can't go back. It's
time to worship God with our giving.